All
right.
All right, y'all. We are live and I am
tiny, but I'll make myself larger. We
are live on this beautiful
uh day. God bless everyone in the name
of Jesus Yeshua, the Messiah. I hope
everyone's super blessed on this Monday
as Bitcoin's dumping, guys. But yeah,
I'm in a little bit of a long trade
here.
I got about 864,000 on the trade.
I'm up about three grand. Unrealized.
Honestly, I'm I've realized I'll
probably get stopped out for like a $700
win
on this trade if if it gets stopped out
here. We're getting a little bit of a
bounce. I'm I'm going to be talking
about what's going to be happening here.
Um, man. So, yeah. Like, here's the
deal, guys. Like, honestly, here's the
deal. The deal is this. I mean,
we rejected from
earlier today the this is basically the
trading plan that I've had like in the
in the Casper crew VIP. So, we get a
move up to the area, we get a rejection,
and now we're down to the support. And
the reason I took this long trade is
because we're bouncing from this area of
support right here. And I do think we
can come lower. All right, I'm treating
this as a scalp trade. I'm very curious
to see what happens now on a back test.
I'm treating this as a scalp trade. And
you know, I did let the community know
in the Casper Crew VIP Discord. I let
the community know a I've taken a trade,
but it's more of like a scalp trade. All
right. And uh looking for a scalp trade.
It's basically like a quick TP.
And yeah, so I hit that TP1 and now like
really we're just going to see what is
going to happen with this one. Uh to be
honest with you, I do feel that we can
make another low and we're going to be
discussing exactly where that's going to
come. So make sure to smash up the
likes, guys. Make sure to subscribe to
the channel. Make sure to click the bell
for notifications cuz we're bringing you
the juiciest live Bitcoin trading videos
in all of YouTube history. Man, let's
see what happens. if we can back test
any of these areas as support or
resistance or what what he is what
whatever it is. Yeah, I'm going to close
this trade. What would be like a $600
profit? And if you're wondering what
happened to my other long, it closed out
today for a $1,000 profit. Jason, you
might say you're such an idiot, you
know, for letting that thing close for a
$1,000 profit when you could have closed
it out for like a $10 $11,000 profit.
That's just the way I trade, guys. You
know, I I I I should just trade that
way, you know. Small win, small win,
small win, small loss, small loss, small
loss, big win. All right. Pretty soon.
Pretty soon, I'm gonna have another
$57,000
win up my sleeve. All right. Pretty
soon, I'm going to have another $57,000
win up my sleeve. You know what?
You know what? I actually I actually
messed up cuz I I closed out that other
long I was in from the from the bottom
by accident, guys.
I made a big mistake over on Antarctic
and I closed out that long that I was in
from the bottom and
it ended up being closed out
for speaking of big wins, it ended up
being closed out for a $54,000 win. It
ended up being closed out for a 50
$52,000 win,
but I didn't mean to close it, but
historically when I close a trade by
accident, it turns out to be kind of
good. All right. So, you know, small
wins, small wins, small loss, small
loss, and then eventually we're going to
lock in those juicy $65,000 wins. Those
juicy $42,000
wins, those juicy 50 How much was that
one? That those juicy $57,000
wins. Wow.
Yeah. Small win, small loss, small win,
small loss. But eventually, man, we're
going to get back to those those those
five figure those six figure.
I have yet to I I have yet to close one
trade for a six figure.
But we will do it, man. We will do it,
men and women. What the heck is wrong
with my camera? You know what? Let me
see if I can fix this. Can I fix my
camera? Camera effects.
The fade level of the green screen.
How's that? Too much. Too much. Let's
see here.
Too much. Too much. Too much.
How's that? It's pretty good. Let's wipe
off the camera there. It's probably got
a little bit of sweat on the camera.
Yeah.
A little bit too much there.
There we go.
Yeah, I think that's kind of good. Ah,
maybe we'll fix a little bit more here.
Yeah, there we go.
Oh, wow. That's fancy. Look at this
office. Isn't that the coolest office
you've ever seen in your life? That is
professional. Talk about a professional
office, man. You can tell I'm a serious
YouTuber with millions of subscribers
with a setup like that. My goodness.
What do you guys think is better? This
or this?
What do you think is better? This or
this? Type in the chat. Say this or this
in the chat. Say this or this. or this
or this. This
or this? All right, just tell me in the
chat. This or this? By the way, speaking
of the chat, big shout out to everybody
in the chat. All right,
shout out to Ruby Connor. Shout out to
Brandon. Shout out to Jesse Gillig.
What's going on, bro? He says, "You and
Cryptoface are boys." Hey, shout out to
Electric Fua. Electric FUA. Imagine
being sad you made 52K. Well, here's the
thing, Khalid Osman. You know what? I'm
not sad I made 52K. I'm happy I made
52K. I'm sad that I closed it out when I
do still think there's a really good
chance we could see Bitcoin hit new
highs. But you know what? Whatever. It
is what it is. Shout out to New Earth
Guardian. I told you guys we're in for a
4 hour sell block and that pump was a
bull trap. He was right. Shout out to
Matt Jason Casper. Do you ever use the
order book? Uh, no. I never use the
order book, man. I don't even know why
they have that thing there. face called
the top of the range at the penny. Think
you did, too. Oh, I mean, you know what?
I have clips of me saying we're
definitely going to dump from here.
Nah, I didn't call the top. I I did not
call the top. I I was very uncertain
about what was going to happen and I'm
still a little bit uncertain. Big shout
out to I enjoy being He says, "Good to
see you, Jason. I also follow your other
YouTube channel."
Uh, should post more. Yeah, I should
post more. I have some stuff I got to
post on that YouTube channel. Shout out
to THR Tiger. Shout out to Rod Schulz.
How low before the bounce. Exciting
times ahead, I believe. Yes. Exciting
times ahead. I'm so dang excited. I'm
about to take off these glasses and put
on a different pair of glasses and shake
my squiggly eye around cuz I'm so dang
excited. I can't wait to see what's
going to happen. Sheesh, man.
Let me put back on these glasses.
These real glasses.
Shout out to Milton from Tartaria. Shout
out to Solomon Mutisa
and ES Carr
and uh Sneak Peak 5167
and Christopher Patrick 1239. Salty TA
with the lime slices. I think those are
limes. Shout out to washing and shout
out to Raw Hayes 196. Nice man. Guess
what? I like your your YouTube logo.
I actually have I have a giant
picture of the same thing right here in
[music] my office. Right here in my
office. Would you look at that? Right
here in this professional office. I've
got myself a giant
a giant one of those, man. A giant one
of those right here in the YouTube
office. I'll keep it right behind me
there in the YouTube office,
you know. Would you look at that? Would
you look at that? Shout out to
Splashfire Films. He says, "Smash the
likes." Smash up the likes. Shout out to
Dimmeret who says, "Win Moon."
Absolutely. Is this a knife catch? I
don't know. You tell me. You tell me. Is
this a knife catch?
Shout out to John 3:16. He bought
Bitcoin. That's what's up, man. Look,
you know, you can't go wrong buying a
little BTC here and there. Why is
Cryptoface the most gangster thing 2026
has bought?
You think Cryptoface is more gangster
than Jason Casper? Jason Casper, the
number one gangster.
Jason Casper's the number one gangster,
you know.
Um,
to the moon. Let's see. I don't know.
It's not looking too moony right here.
Bitcoin I feel like is going to moon us.
Shout out to Jay Becker. Good afternoon.
God bless. Hit them likes. I got 1,400.
[music]
Got 14,500 steps. What about y'all? How
many steps y'all have? All right. How
many steps y'all have? Let Let me
actually move this out of the way here.
How many steps y'all have so far today?
I I have about 15,000 today. About
15,000 steps today. Bitcoin getting a
little bit of a pump. Is this a knife
catch? The answer is yes, guys. You
know, we came down to a level. We came
down to a naked weekly point of control.
That's why we're getting a bounce here.
All right. This is the plan in the
Casper crew that we had since when did
we have this? Since, let me find out. I
can find out right now. We had it since
August 1st. This is our plan since
August. This is how long it takes for
Bitcoin to move. All right. This is our
plan since August 1st in the Casper crew
BIP discord. And yeah, when we came down
to this level, I decided to take the
trade. All right. Now, I'm treating as a
scalp trade. I'm not expecting much, but
if we get a lot, I'll take it. But I'm
not expecting much. Right. I told the
community that I'm not going to long
until we come lower. Right? I'm trying
to keep people updated as we go. I'm
telling them, look, I'm not longing now.
I'm waiting for lower. If I decide to
long, I'll let you know. Let everyone
know, okay, I've taken the long because
we had the plan and I'm treating as a
scalp trade, right? Mark Ciper B has
room to make another low. Let everyone
know I hit my TP1. Let the rest sizzle
like Miss Frile from the Magic School
Bus. You guys ever watch that show? The
Magic School Bus.
A pretty good show. You're probably
missing out if you don't watch it. All
right. Shout out to R. Pink. Two Miles
just 6,000 steps. Why did I stop
rapping? Cuz Jason Casper is the number
one gangster.
Um.
All right. All right. All right. Let's
pop into the charts. Let's pop right
into the charts. But right now, I I'm
just so curious to see if Bitcoin's
going to get another another little
green candle. We got another little
green candle coming on up. Man, I'm so
dang excited. You know, I just live my
life for the green candles. I live my
life for the green candles,
you know.
I live my life for the green candles.
Uh
yeah,
I live my life for the green candles.
Hey yo, [music] I live my life for the
green candles. Walking on the treadmill,
wearing sandals
cuz I don't want blisters. Jake Casper
only brother with the sisters. Yeah, cuz
Jay Casper's a gangster.
That's all I got.
That's all I got. All right. Um, let's
actually pop into the chart. So, here's
the thing. We're coming down to this
zone
and let's let's pop on over to a fresh
clean chart here. All right. Let's let's
come over to a a fresh clean chart. All
right. will clean off everything right
now. So, we are bouncing from a naked
point of control. But here's the deal.
The Bitcoin price lately, guys, has been
forming this disgusting range, this
disgusting channel. And yesterday, I
said, I don't know what's going to
happen, but this channel is going to
break. And if it breaks to the downside,
well, there's a really good chance we
give it all back. All right, if we give
it all back, we're coming down a little
bit lower to around $63,000.
And that's going to be around well the
Fibonacci golden pocket and the 786. So
right now here's what I'm expecting to
happen. I'm expecting that this little
bounce here is going to be just that a
little bounce that's going to eventually
give us a lower low. And I'll tell you
why I think that. Now first of all like
we we are bouncing from this key
support. But the main level that we have
down here at 634, we also have a daily
level and a weekly level down there and
it's the Fibonacci golden pocket. And
that's where we'll officially take all
the liquidity from this channel. We'll
come right back down into this zone,
which is pretty much the key support
zone right here. And if we take a look
at all of this, right? We look at all
this sloop. It's also the value area low
of the range. All right. So, in my
opinion, highest probability right now
is that we do come down lower. That
doesn't mean we can't get a bit of a
bounce here. All right. We'll have to
see what happens. Can we even make a
higher high right here? I don't know. I
don't know. But so far, I'd say
excellent job for a scalp for a
scalperoni and cheese. Yeah, I'll take
it. I'll take it for a little bit of a
scalp, you know. But, um, that's what I
think is most likely happen next. And
also, we take a look at like our our
lower time frames like the 12minut. You
can see here that the 12minut doesn't
have the best looking divergence in the
world. What it does have, and what I
will give the 12-minute right now is the
money flow. All right, but it doesn't
have the divergence. What I would love
to see here is something like this
happen where maybe we come up a little
bit, we back test the PC at around 64
and then we get another drop and that
other drop gives us the confident uneven
beautiful butt cheek pattern with the
big old fat juicy on the left, skinny on
the right. Man oh man, drives me wild to
see this. There's nothing I love more
than looking at these butt cheeks. In
fact, what I like to do is I like to put
on my Inspectacles.
As you can see, I've got my Inspecticles
on. I even take a magnifier, the
Inspectical magnifier, and I zoom in on
the cheeks. All right, I zoom right in
to see if I can see any bullish
divergences.
All right, so that's what we're waiting
for right now to see if we see any
bullish divergences. We got our inspects
on. We know what we want to see and
we're waiting. Ah, big purple candle
coming in. We see we might not even have
time to form the inspectical butt cheek
pattern here. But we are forming some
big butt cheek uh big boy green dots
here on the 12-minute time frame. Uh-oh.
Oh man, we're losing the blue line
again. This is not good. This blue line
on the chart, this was the level we
need. Oh. Oh, big old green candle. Come
on, baby. Come on, bitty itty bitty
Bitcoin getting a big old bounce. We
need a big green candle here right now.
Okay, now here's the deal. If we cannot
hold the value area low of this range
around $63,000
we're going to call it, right? Then I do
believe we're going to come down to the
$60,000 zone cuz that is actually if we
take a look at all this here
and we just look at this more macro
range, if we lose the local range, then
guess what? We're coming to value area
low of macro range. That's going to be
around 60 60ish to $61,000. All right.
So, those are my two targets to the
downside here. All right. My two targets
to the downside is number one around
64K, 635 to 64K. If we can't hold that,
then I expect that we're coming down
lower. And the reason for these two
targets is simply just the ranges,
right? If we're going to take a look at
this as a sideways range, well, the
value area low, that's the place where
we expect to come. And if we lose that
value area low, then we expect to come
down to the value area low of the more
macro range. All right. Now, what about
short trades right now? Well, I don't
really think there's a short trade to be
had right here. If I'm going to be
totally honest, the short trade to be
had was up here. I was asleep for it,
but I've been long. I've been publicly
long since
when was when did we come up to around
when was that? I have been publicly
short. I'm sorry. Since I think the 27th
of July.
So, I've been short for a long time.
I've held shorts all this time, right?
So, I' I've been in shorts. Uh, but this
trade, I didn't actually take it, but
the setup was given and it happened when
I was not at the charts. All right.
Happened Sunday, August 9th at 16:00,
which is when? 4:00 p.m. I guess I
wasn't around at 400 p.m. All right. I
guess I wasn't around at at 400 p.m. Um,
big shout out to uh Darren does things.
What's going on, Darren? He says,
"Jason, tell me it's going to be okay.
I'm scared and running around like a
wild woman in distress.
Look, bro, it's going to be okay. But if
you find yourself running around like a
wild woman in distress, looking like
Janet Yellen, what I like to do is take
deep breaths into the plunger,
you know? Um,
yeah. Yeah, your boy watches The Magic
School Bus, Houston. That's what's up,
man. That's my favorite show. I don't
watch TV every day, but when I do watch
TV every day, I watch the Magic School
Bus every day. What kind of cheese goes
best with a scalperoni? Well, right now,
raw Swiss. Raw Swiss. Because I'll tell
you, I get my cheese from a local farm
and we just get a whole bunch of
whatever kind of cheeses they make. And
right now, we have a block of raw Swiss
open. So, that's the one I'm eating on
all my scalps. Raw Swiss. Hopefully, my
slice doesn't have too many holes. All
right.
Um,
for sure, for sure. Cardano. Everyone
wants to, everyone wants to look at
Cardano. By everyone, I mean D major. D
major. Will I open a long from 60K?
I don't know yet, but if I do, I'll let
the Casper crew VIP Discord know. Just
like I let them know I was taking this
scalp long trade. And just like I let
them know I longed the exact bottom
at $57,000.
I don't have I don't have the image.
Dang it. Well, like I said, I
accidentally closed the trade out. All
right, this trade right here from 584.
I told the Casper crew I I took this
trade.
I closed it out by accident. Oh,
I closed it out by accident. It's crazy,
man. Open on June 25th.
Open on June 25th.
So, we longed it in the exact bottom on
June 25th,
and now it's closed out by accident. Oh
my goodness. What a terrible, horrible
thing to do. What a terrible, horrible
thing to do.
I hate closing trades by accident. It's
the second time in the last month I've
closed a trade by accident. Last time,
it sent me into a spiral of bad trading
psychology, revenge trading. I was up
all night sniffing lines of blue candles
trying to get the price to pump.
I was scraping the blue candles off my
hat, hoping just to get a little bit of
residue, put it in my pipe full of opium
and smoke this thing up. I'm not ready
for that again, guys. I'm not ready for
that again. All right, Jesse Gil, I'm
making $20 here and $30 there sometimes.
That's what's up, man. Am I going for
the weekly candle and the the CC Senor
Jason?
I don't know.
What is the CC?
But there is a weekly and a daily right
next to each other right here. That is
the next place I'm looking to take
along. Man, if this if this one doesn't
turn out,
let's check out actually let's look at
let's look at the good old market monkey
right here. Let's go to the one minute
market monkey and see what's happening.
Oh, baby.
Wow. Traders are opening up positions
here.
They are opening up positions.
It's interesting. It's pretty pretty
even right now. Longs and shorts. We got
a big spike in volume. Would you look at
this? Wow.
Big spike in volume. Big increase in
open interest. Let's see if this volume
can't push us up a little bit higher,
man. Will this turn into something juicy
or will I just fall flat on my face?
Will I just fall flat on my face,
you know?
At least I did look it in as Crypto
Crank would say. Absolutely. We've
looked it in, baby. We've looked it in.
Remember when you messed up and made
56K? Good times. Yeah, I did it twice in
a row, bro. I did it twice in a row.
Twice in a row. Swiss cheese.
Let's see. Swiss cheese. fasting 24
hours and going for more. Don't talk
about food. Sorry, Splash Fire films.
Splashfire's on a fast.
I need I need to I need to start
fasting. I need to start fast. It's been
a It's been a while since I did a proper
fast. More than 24 hour. It's been a pro
It's been a while. I need to do a 48 48
hour fast or more. That's what I need. I
need to do a 48 hour fast.
You know, reset the digestion. spend
some time in prayer. You know what I'm
saying?
The more holes, the closer to God.
I don't know exactly what you mean by
that, but I live streamed Sunday at 1. I
know. I know. And then I shut the
computer and didn't look at the charts
until this morning after we got that
drop.
Uh they missed all the short liquidity
above 654. Yeah, maybe they go for it
now. I mean, it is a false move Monday.
And you know what? If I was Carl from
the moon, baby, I would be drawing a
bull flag right now, making a video.
And you know what? Secretly,
I am Carl from the moon.
So, here we go, baby. This is our
target. We're shooting for $64,000 back
test P. Let's see if we can't get up to
the $64,000 P of our range is coming up
right here. 653
64K. Yeah, I I think yeah, let's let's
get a back test of the PC. Come on,
baby. Yeah, we got some ugly bearish
divs on the four. That is really an ugly
bearish div on the four. I'm not going
to lie.
Let's go to the 1 hour.
Yeah, honestly, to me, it looks like
based on our 1 hour, I think we're going
to do something like this and roll over
after we back test this guy here.
And then we can come down either to this
value area low right around here or we
come down to the big setup, the big one.
The big one. And you know what's
interesting?
There's two ways you can read the big
one. Either big one or bygon. Depends on
where you put the hyphen. We're looking
for the bygon, baby. Or the big one. It
depends on where you put the hyphen.
We're going for the bygon, baby. Well,
bygon.
We're going for the bygon, baby. I'm
always going for the bygon.
Put a one in the chat if you're going
for the bygon.
Do I think Bitcoin will go under 50K by
October? I don't know. I hope it will.
Why does a 48 hour fast seem so slow?
Because the fasting doesn't start to
feel easy until after the 72-hour mark.
So after the 3 days of fasting, then it
starts to become easier.
But the 42, that's that's where it's
real intense cuz a 24-hour fast, that's
nothing, right? You know, we do that all
the time. I at least I do that all the
time by accident. I wake up, I work out,
I trade Bitcoin, I take care of the
chickens, I cut the grass, I play with
the kids, I do the dishes. Next thing I
know, it's been 24 hours since I ate
dinner and it's time for dinner,
right?
So, it's like when you go to bed
having not eaten anything the next day
and then you wake up having eaten
nothing yesterday and then you go for
the next day, you know, that's that
feels a little strange. That's that's
hard to do. But once you get past that
3-day mark, then you get that uh that
that faster high. All right. Some people
say that's your cells auto faging
themselves,
right? It's just your cells autoaging.
They're autoaging themselves. It feels
good when you autoage.
All right? But other people say, "No,
it's not autoagy.
It's your cortisol spiking so high cuz
your body's in starvation mode, freaking
out. Your cortisol is freaking out. So,
you got that cortisol high. You know
what I'm saying? That good feeling you
get when you wake up first thing in the
morning, set an alarm for 4:30 a.m.,
slap yourself in the face and say,
"Don't be a pussy." And then you do 20
burpees on the floor, chug a giant glass
of black coffee you have on the side of
the bed. Then, while you're still out of
breath and panting, you go into the cold
shower and smack yourself more on the
face. Go downstairs, do 300 pull-ups,
300 push-ups, go out and shovel some
snow
before you even start your day. That's
the kind of cortisol I'm talking about,
baby.
That cortisol feels kind of good for a
while until all of a sudden
you're questioning your sanity and all
that stuff. Oh man, Carl from the moon
strikes again, baby. We're pumping out.
We're pumping out.
You heard it. You heard it here first.
The Jason Casper channel. We're pumping
out, baby. Let's get a rocket ship on
here. How do we get a rocket ship?
Where's my rocket ship?
Bitcoin's about to blast. We'll get the
volcano up in here.
All right, here we go, baby. Oh, yeah.
This is what I'm talking about.
You're on 1,800 calories today, bro. Oh
my goodness. Do I think a vasectomy goes
against God's design for men? That's a
good question as I'm highly considering
myself becoming fixed and getting a
vasectomy. But it, you know what? I
don't know. I can't answer that. I can't
answer that. You know, I I could give a
case for two different scenarios. You
know, you know, why don't we ask why
don't we ask the Pope? The Pope will
tell us.
You know,
I don't know. I don't know cuz I have I
I I keep making babies. I just keep
making babies all day and all night. I
don't know how it happens either, you
know? So, I don't know. I don't know.
Here's the thing. Like when it comes to
having kids, you know, I want to be able
to pour into my children. I want to be
able to spend time with them, quality
time pouring into them. I've known a lot
of families with really big families and
and the parents don't get to pour into
their kids. They have like 8, nine, 10
kids, and I feel like the kids, they
they fall through the cracks. They fall
through the cracks. They don't get
poured into like they need, right?
That's that's my one concern about
having a lot of kids to be honest with
you. Cuz even now with four kids, it is
hard to give them all the quality time
that they need. You know what I'm
saying? Individually,
but know that this is a crypto this is a
crypto stream. All right? So, we're not
going to be talking about snipping our
tubes up in here. You know what I'm
saying?
Um,
do I still average 5,000 calories a day
even when I fast like that? Uh, if I'm
going to do a 24-hour fast, then I'll
probably end up with like 4,500
4,000 calories that day. Maybe 3,800.
Uh-oh. CDW. Oh my goodness. Flip the
volcano upside down, guys. We just got a
swing failure pattern of the high. You
know, we just got a swing failure
pattern of the high. Time for an
inverted volcano.
H, I should have taken a profit too up
there.
Oh, take profit too should have
happened. Oh my goodness. A rapid
rejection.
A rapid rejection.
Oh my goodness. A rapid rejection. Oh,
but a back test.
Oh my goodness. Do you see that?
Holy crap. A rapid rejection. The
Bitcoin price switches direction. Makes
me sit down and makes me reflection.
Bitcoin price inverse erection dumping
down to the floor. But I got to come
back for a little more. We got the green
candle about to back test the trend
line. [music] Then we pump to the sky
and we're looking fine. We got the Carl
from the moon. Bitcoin price coming in
baby about to zoom. Got the volcano
pattern and boom. The Greek candles
pumping straight up to the zoom to the
moon to the zoom. If there is no more
room to hear the price of the dry peach
is a prune.
Just kidding. It's a plum. Bitcoin
little baby sucking thumb. H we got a
nice bottom here. We got the [music]
support and then we're in the clear cuz
we came for the double bottom. Can you
spot them about to rob them? Then we're
popping up like we're drumming John
Bonum. Let Zeppelin change direction.
Bitcoin price an inverse erection to
switch the direction. Get the vasectomy
the Bitcoin price. Now listen to me.
We're up $1,700.
But if you're feeling bullish, let me
hear you holler. Jay Casper t-shirt, no
collar. We [music] got the tank top
coming in. It's to holler at your boy.
His name is Jay. What do you say? We're
trading Bitcoin every other day and I
give it to you straight. You know I
never give a gay. I'm so dang serious,
baby. No, I never play. I'm outside in
the garden ding with the spade. I'm so
hungry every day. I'm eating from the
trades. Got the tray. We don't play Jay
Casper. Another day.
Okay.
H man, this is really this is really
this is an inverse. An inverse. Here we
go. Oh, by the way guys, the egg code is
summer. All right. Egg code is summer.
Egg code is summer.
All right, check it out. What's the
target of the Bitcoin trade? I guess
zero. Now it was 100K. Now it's zero.
Look at this simple swing failure
pattern of the high. Mini range swing
failure pattern low. Swing failure
pattern of the high. We're going down to
zero right now. We're legit going to
sero. Cero
meo. Eromano,
man. Look at this. We are losing money
quick. We are losing money quick.
[sighs]
Yeah, we got these red candles. Oh my
goodness. Buy signal about to print on
the 1 hour cipher. Ah,
do you think that's a buy signal on the
1 hour cipher or is this setting us up
for an anchor wave? I think this is
setting us up for an anchor wave to be
followed by a trigger and the trigger
probably could happen around 644 63K or
if not we come straight down to the the
big one that we've been waiting for. Of
course, I don't say big one. I say bygon
cuz it's spelled the same way. Bygon,
right? I'm waiting for a bygon. Let
bygones be bygones.
Shout out to Felix H from the France.
Um, yeah, the egg code is summer. All
right, if you know what it is, you can
get some eggs. Guys, just a quick
reminder, every single week, Bitbase is
giving away $500. In fact, you know
what? We're going to do a $500 giveaway
today. If you're interested in that,
sign up to Bitbase. Also, guys, remember
Blofin.
Blofin is giving away $2,000 a week. We
just gave away $2,000 this morning
courtesy of Blofin in the Casper Crew
live stream. Here's the thing. You don't
have to be a VIP member in order to win
this money to trade with. All you have
to do is sign up to Blowofin and Bitbase
using my links for Blowfin. You have to
sign up to my free Discord and follow
the instructions.
But for Bitbase, you literally just have
to sign up. And right now, we're about
to give away $500
courtesy of Bitbase.
All right. Very low fees, VIP level
seven fees for blowoffin and bibase.
You're getting the juiciest fees.
No KYC, no VPN. Juicy fees.
Money giveaway every time. Every week.
Shout out to preparing for war. Oh man.
I got an itch on the back. Woo. Do I
have any rooster chickens? Of course I
do. Are you kidding me? What do you
think? I want my flock of chickens to be
infertile.
You think I want to have infertile
chickens?
Just like I don't People ask Jason, do
you grow seedless watermelons? You think
I want my melons to be infertile?
You think I want to castrate my melons?
Castrate my chicken coupe? Heck no. Of
course, we got roosters in there. And
they have big rooster balls. Let me tell
you, you can't tell unless you kill
them. Cuz the roosters, they're they're
they have uh their their balls are
inside of them. All right? They don't
they don't droop out. They're inside.
All right? In fact,
I've eaten them. I've eaten rooster
balls. You heard it here first. Jason
Casper eats rooster balls. All right.
You know, you you you the you eat those
chicken organs. When you when you
harvest your own chicken, you eat the
heart, the liver, the kidneys. The only
thing I don't eat is the lungs. I don't
know. They always kind of freak me out.
The heart, the liver, the kidneys. Loses
as we call them in Espano. Actually, los
bolleos. Los bolleos is how you say
balls. The balls in Spanish. Los
bolleos.
Yeah. You eat everything. You put it in
the chicken soup. People like, "What's
this? Is this a giant kidney bean?"
People come over for dinner. We're
having chicken soup. They're like, "Is
this a big kidney bean?" I'm like, "Yes,
[laughter]
sure. Sure,
sure. Yeah, sure. Whatever makes you
sleep better at night, man. Whatever
makes you sleep better at night, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Um,
no, not Los Kones. Los Bleos. See, see,
summit trade signals. No, Los Palos.
See? See?
Los
the eggs. You know, I'm all about the
Huevos, by the way.
Um,
yeah, the lungs creep me out. The other
stuff doesn't creep me out. I don't know
what it is. I mean, I don't know. I
guess I I guess the lungs is such a
spongy, chewy kind of material. Like
when those little shriveled up lungs,
it's hard to scrape the lungs. If you
ever scraped out a chicken's organs
where you shove your hand up where the
intestines used to be and you scrape out
all the organs and you pull them out and
they all fall out, the lungs get stuck
up in there inside like the rib cage.
You got to go in there and scrape out
the lungs with your fingernails
[music] and they're all spongy and
stuff. But sometimes if you get a
chicken, let's say you get a whole
chicken, you just roast a whole chicken
in the oven. It's still got a little
lung in there. All right. Still got a
little lung left in there. It's very
spongy and chewy and it's kind of I just
don't like it. I've tried it. I'm not a
big fan of the lung. All right.
Not a big fan of the lung. Yeah, lung
does have a weird texture.
Wait,
are you serious? Doc the goat. Someone
tried to blow himself up. Someone blew
himself up trying to kill us. You picked
up his lungs after they got blown 30 ft
away.
Okay. I don't know what human lungs are
like.
But yeah.
All right. We're getting a little bit of
a green candle, but it looks like we're
rejecting from the local golden pocket
here. We've made a lower low.
Let's see. Yeah, look at this. Rejecting
from the local 61ita. If we can clear
this, guys, then we're in the clear. We
need to clear this to be in the clear.
Come on, baby. $800,000 on the trade.
Sam's eating dinner. Hopefully, you're
not eating lungs. Are you eating liver,
kidneys, heart, testicles?
Cuz I eat that stuff all the time. I'm
not even kidding. Liver, kidneys, heart,
testicles. I eat it all. I eat it all.
Spleen. A little bit of spleen.
You know,
a little bit of pancreas here and there.
You know what I'm saying? Oh, no. A big
juicy red candle.
A big juicy red candle.
Do chickens have tongues? No, they
don't. They don't. You're eating sausage
casserole. Well, that's the thing about
sausages. You never know what's in that
thing, man. You probably got heart,
liver, kidney, eyeballs, tongue, and all
a whole bunch of stuff in that stuff.
Unless you made it yourself. You know,
that's good old mystery meat. Put it all
in the grinder and fill it up in some
intestines, you got yourself a a
sausage, suppose. Tastes good though,
doesn't it? And I'll tell you what else
tastes good. Heart, liver, kidneys,
oils pumping. Oh man, this is bad for
Bitcoin. This is real bad,
man. I think we might get stopped out of
this one, guys. I think we might get
stopped out of this one.
That's okay. We'll get stopped out for a
couple hundred profit and then we'll try
and hop back in. We'll try and hop back
in.
Can chickens fly?
You know what? Yeah, kind of. But not I
haven't seen a chicken fly like like a
blackbird or a bluebird,
but if their wings get long enough, they
can go up into trees and stuff.
Uh, you know, um, ground beef is
suspicious, too. Especially my ground
beef spicy noodle. Let me tell you, the
ground beef I eat is full of a whole
bunch of strange stuff.
The ground beef I eat is full of hearts
and kidneys and livers and all that
stuff, man. I'll tell you. Just grind it
all up. Mix it all together. Mix it all
together.
But
yeah,
take a break even. No, I'm not going to
take a break even. I'm going to let it
close out for a $600 profit. It's going
to be around a $600 profit. May maybe
maybe a $500 profit by the time the fees
are in. I don't know if this calculates
the fees or not. I don't know if this
stop loss price calculates the fees or
not. Shout out to D Crypto. Shout out to
Doc the Goat. Turkeys fly. Wild turkeys
fly. Shout out to Aram 7912. Hopes I win
the trade. Thank you. I will win. I will
win the trade. Either a small win or a
big win. Duck eggs are better than
chicken eggs. You know what? They are
bigger. They kind of taste the same to
me, but sadly I don't have ducks. So,
and I won't get ducks. They don't fit
the homestead,
you know.
Ew. But holes and teeth, ground beef.
That's disgusting. That's disgusting.
All right.
That's disgusting, man. That's
disgusting.
You know, yeah, wild turkeys fly. We
have flocks of wild turkeys that often
times come in our backyard, and I like
them. I I I try and talk to them. I say,
"Hey, look, look, if you guys stick
around here, I'll feed you. I'll clothe
you. I'll put you up in the hen house.
You could be friends with my chickens."
But then when I try and when I try and
come close, they fly away. They fly
away. You know, they come out, the the
the the the male turkeys spread their
feathers,
you know.
What's my favorite organ to eat? I don't
know. I'll be honest with you. I I don't
know. I don't have a favorite organ to
eat. I don't have a favorite or organ to
eat. The only reason I eat organ meat is
because they say they say it's good for
you. And they knows everything. They
knows everything. They is responsible
for everything. They knows everything.
They is trying to hide everything from
you.
You know, they are secretly trying to
kill you. They are trying to keep you
stupid. And they also say organs are
good for you. So the same people that
are trying to kill you and make you a
vegan are are the same they that's
trying to make you eat organ meat. I
mean you they cannot be trusted. But
they do say organ meat is highly
nutrient-dense. I mean what could go
wrong? Liver's a filter. It filters out
all the gross stuff. I mean why is that
weird? You would eat your car filter or
your air filter, right? What could go
wrong with eating a filter? Sounds super
healthy. Sounds amazing. No wonder they
recommend it to you.
You know it's the filter. It cleans out
all the garbage. You know, who wouldn't
want to eat a garbage filter?
They say it's good, so it must be good.
You think that McDonald's is made of
human meat? Soilent green.
McDonald's is the real Soilent green.
You know,
they them pronouns.
Shout out to Stop Profits Take Lost. I
like that YouTube name. Who are they?
They you they. That's their name is
they. Their name is they.
Have you found a way to keep roosters
from cockadoodle doing? No, man. You got
to let them cockadoodle do.
You've got to let them cockadoodle do.
My favorite is when they go through
puberty and they get this half
cockadoodle. It's like [clears throat]
cockadoo. Their voice starts cracking.
They go from little chickep to
And then one morning they wake up with a
big strong manly cockadoodle do. Man, I
miss my rooster Sam Bankman fried
chicken. He got eaten. He got eaten by a
fox. Sam Bankman Fried Chicken got eaten
by a fox. Guys, isn't that the saddest
thing you ever heard? Oh [sighs] man, I
miss Sam Bankman Fried Chicken. Let me
see if I could find him. Sam Bankman
Fried Chicken.
Let's see here.
Oh man, we have to go way back in time.
We have to go way back in time to find
Sam Bankman Fried Chicken.
Where is Sam Bankman Fried Chicken? I
have some weird shorts on here, guys,
honestly.
There's the watermelons.
Sam Begman Fried Chicken.
Let's see. We got to go back in time
even farther here.
>> Oh, Sam Begman Fried Chicken. Here he
is.
>> All right, y'all. This is so shocking.
You are not going to
>> Oh, this is not it.
>> That's not the right video.
>> Oh man, I miss Sambang Fried Chicken so
much.
Let's see if I can
copy the link and post it in a new tab
here to find Sam Bangman Fried Chicken.
Here he is. There he is. Sam Bankman
Fried Chicken.
He is He was a beautiful rooster.
He died. Look at Look at his neck
feathers. Look at those neck feathers.
You see how beautiful? Oh man. Hang on.
>> Yeah. Hang on.
There we go. Look at that beautiful
rooster, Sam Bankman Fried Chicken. He
got eaten by a fox. The poor thing. But
the reason why he was named Sam Begman
Fried Chicken is cuz he was screwing all
the other chickens.
Look at him. See, he was all about
screwing over all those other just your
common chicken out there just like Sam
Bagman free would screw over all the
common crypto people. So, we named him
Sam Bagman Fried Chicken.
There he goes. Look, he doesn't even
care after. He doesn't even spend the
night. He just is right out. He's just
right out ready for the next one.
>> Sam Bankman fried chicken now.
>> I love Sam Begman fried chicken. I miss
I miss Samman fried. I miss SPF.
How's our Bitcoin trade doing?
I know, right? He looks like a painting.
I know.
When was the FTX crash? November 2022.
you know, um,
man, we got to give a big shout out to
the super chat in here. Jay, can you
explain what is a nc?
I don't know what an NC PC is,
but a a naked point of control in better
in general is a point of control that's
never been touched by the price. So, for
example, these naked naked weekly and
naked daily point of controls. I don't
know what a naked C I don't know what
the C would stand for. This stands for
naked weekly, naked daily. This goes
back to the day
that we had over here. This day right
over here,
uh, this was the point of control of the
day. All right, this is the highest
volume node of the day
and this was the highest volume node of
last week. And so if if a candle forms a
high volume node, a big candle like
this, this is where most of the volume
was. and then the next daily candle
never comes down to touch that price. It
leaves you behind. It's naked. All
right. Honestly, if you want to know
more about this, you can always watch my
video on Sam Bank and Fried Chicken or
you can go to Jason Casper's account.
You can go to playlists and check out
the free trading course cuz I'm pretty
sure I have multiple videos on volume.
All right.
Uh
Naked Points of Control Explained. Wow.
a whole video on it in my free course,
Naked Points of Control. Free trading
course, nine out of 18. All right,
so that's what's up. All right, go check
it out. The free course. All right. Oh,
Bitcoin pumping, baby. We should have
taken profit here the first time. Will
we take profit here the second time?
[laughter]
No. But we will take a screenshot to
post it on Twitter, baby. Cuz you know
what? That's all that counts. You know,
as long as people think you're making
money, that's all that counts, baby.
Look, since I took the screenshot, we're
already down $200, $300.
But it's okay. I'll post this on Twitter
and brag about my juicy profits that I
never took. You know, it's a skill. It's
an art. It's an art form. Taking a
screenshot of your unrealized P&L is an
art form.
Big shout out to the Living BAM8 for the
super chat VIP member here. Thanks for
everything. God bless you. I like uh
your picture there. It's pretty crazy.
Thank you so much for the super chat. I
really appreciate you, man.
SPF is chilling with his friends in
prison.
Man, my poor rooster. I had roosters
kick me in the leg with their spurs.
Yes, they do that. They get very uh
feisty.
Yeah. Yeah. So, here's what I do.
Honestly, I know pe people are going to
think this is crazy, but what I do is if
a rooster tries to get violent with me,
I kick him in the face. And then I push
him down. I take my fingers, I put them
on his neck, and I push his face down to
the ground. And I hold him there for a
while. I hold him there for a while just
to let him know I'm the alpha rooster.
And I give him a big old
And I'm not even kidding. that actually
does. When you show your dominance like
that, they'll think you're the head the
the head rooster of the pecking order.
I'm not even kidding. You don't kick
them hard. You're not trying to hurt
them, but they're coming towards you.
They're trying to lunch at you. Give
them a nice little kick in the face. All
right. Nice little boom right in the
face. And then you push them down on the
ground. Push them down. Hold them down.
Make them sit and put your two fingers
over their neck so that their face is on
the ground. And you hold it there for a
while. You got You might have to do that
for a few days. And then eventually
they'll learn, you know what, Jason
Casper is a true alpha rooster. You
know, cuz here's the thing, chickens
don't have the best eyesight. If you
guys were to see me on the street,
you know, you would see, wow, that man
is an alpha rooster. That man is a
straightup alpha rooster.
But chickens don't have the best
eyesight. So, they can't use their eyes
to see that Jason Casper is an alpha
rooster. They need a little bit of extra
help. You know what I'm saying? A little
bit of extra help.
Um,
roosters are straight up buttholes.
Sometimes you have to punt those efforts
just to show dominance. I mean, they can
be, but I've also had some nice rooster.
I I've had, you know, they they they run
the gamut. It depends on how high their
testosterone is. You know what I'm
saying? You get a liberal rooster, super
low testosterone. They're very nice.
They're very nice. Everything they have,
they share. They hold everything in
common. They're basically like
communists. All right. Get a little bit
more higher testosterone rooster.
Straight up libertarian. You come on his
property, he's trying to get you. All
right. You come on his property, he's
trying to get you.
You know what I'm [music] saying?
But if a rooster tries to get you, I'll
tell you what to do. I'll tell you what
to do. If a rooster tries to get you,
I'll tell you what to do. Put his face
on the ground and go cockadoodle do.
Then he'll [music] know that you're the
alphaaroo. He won't mess with you when
you come into his crew. Baby, we got a
low T rooster. He's super liberal.
[music] Call him a booster cuz he loves
to get his booster shots. Dr. Fouchy
coming in with a nice blot plot. And
then they let you into their property
and they say it's so nice. How did ED?
[music]
But the liberal roosters, they got low
tea. But the libertarian ones between
you and me pumping up with the big
testicle [music]
days, [singing] they will attack you.
They'll say, "Hey Jay, get off my
property if you want to live."
But then [music] you got to give the
rooster and show him who's boss. Sick
his face in some applesauce. Make him
eat the sauce and [music] tell him I'm
the boss. Jay Casper only taking wins
and never los cuz I am the trading boss.
But you know I got to show my dominance
with the gloss. So you take the rooster.
How do you do? Push his head down and go
cockadoodle do. You might have to give
him a little kick too. Make sure he
knows that you're the true alpha
rooster. The alpha rooster. I'm [music]
a top G baby. Alpha rooster. Jason
coming out cockadoodle dooster. [music]
I'm a top G. I'm the alpha rooster. Jake
Casper the alpha rooster. Coming out
like cockadoodle dooster. [music]
Pulling out my glockadoodle dooster.
Give them nice little cockadoodle
boomster. You got to show your
dominance. Bitcoin price do the little
dance. You got a problem with your
rooster. Sit back. I'mma show you what
to do. Sir, push his face down into the
ground. Give a little cockadoodle do
sound. Jay Casper always turning around
just to see if the roosters are coming
through the town.
Oh. Oh man,
this trade is probably not going to go
so well, honestly.
Yeah, it's kind of the same. How much
TRT to give your beta rooster?
It depends, man. It depends.
It depends.
Yeah, I don't know what's going to
happen here. We're consolidating, I
guess. I want to pump. I want to pump. I
want to take profits, but I can't I I
can only take screenshots.
I can only take screenshots. All right.
Liver prank says we're about Level Prank
says we're about to pop to the upside.
Hang on. I I got to What the heck? Hang
on a second.
Uh
that was 1 hour ago.
I hope we pop to the upside, man. I
really do.
Did I get some of that remmineralizing
gum? No, but I did get some remineral
remminizing
toothpowder, [music] you know,
remmineralizing toothpowder.
Um,
and what's just going to happen with
this?
My rooster is the biggest booster.
All right. I hope we do pop to the
upside a little bit. What's the next
level you're looking for? IGF, this
fails.
Um, the next level I'm looking for in
case this fails is going to be around
63K. around 63K.
All right. All right. So, we're going to
do our Bitbase giveaway, guys. All
right. We're going to do our Bitbase
giveaway. Here's what we got to do. To
do our Bitbase $500 giveaway, just spam
the chat with your Bitbase user ID
[music]
and then we will we will airdrop you the
dang whatchamacall.
The dang whatchamacall. See?
Yeah, I'll air we'll aird drop you the
500 USDT. All right, but right now I
need everyone to spam the chat with
their you uh with their bybit user ID.
All right, [music] and we're going to
count down from 10
and we're going to take a screenshot.
All right, here we go. 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3
2 1 boom.
All right, the winner is Krypto for
Columbus. Krypto for Columbus.
Congratulations, Krypto for Columbus.
Crypto for Columbus.
Let's see here.
Crypto for Columbus. Got your Got you
right here, bro. Look at this. Crypto
for Columbus. He's the one highlighted.
Crypto for Columbus.
Congrats, bro.
So, I'm going to send this over to
Bitbase and they're going to airdrop you
500 smackarels. US Donald Trump's USDTS,
baby.
Big shout out to Chris.
Crypto for Columbus.
Krypto for Columbus. Columbus.
There's a Columbus among us. Don't eat
the fungus.
Have I ever thought of streaming on
kick? I'm not sure exactly what that is.
Remember, I am a baby boomer.
All right, big shout out to y'all, man.
And guys, here's the thing. We're gonna
we're Yeah, I should take another
screenshot of this profit now that we're
up again. Listen, listen, listen. What
was I going to say?
I forget. I forget what I was going to
say. I forget what I was going to say.
Um
Oh, I remember what I was going to say.
Guys, we do this every single week.
Every single week on these public
streams, we're giving away $500 from
BitBase. We're giving away $2,000 a week
on Blowfin.
All right. $2,000 a week on Blowin. And
you know what? Sometimes I just give
away money in general. Sometimes I just
randomly give away money in general. In
fact, if we can come up to this, if we
can back test $64,000,
I'm going to give away on this stream,
I'll give away $250
to a random viewer. I don't know if we
can do it. Let's see. Baby, I'm not a
millennial. I'm I'm a I'm a baby boomer.
There was a big boom of babies when my
parents got back from fighting World War
II and they saw each other for the first
time in years. They made passionate love
and I was the product. Jason Casper, the
alpha rooster, a product of passionate
love making after the war. Tie a yellow
ribbon around the old oak tree. Cuz I'll
be here when you come back, baby. It's
what my mom said to my dad.
Thankfully, my dad made it back. And
here I am. Jason Casper, the alpha
rooster. My parents are so proud. A true
boomer. An alpha rooster. Talking to
text all the time, speaker phone all the
time.
That's just how I roll, baby.
Let's see. Let's see.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Are we going to pump up to the to the
blue line? I think we can pump up to the
blue line. Bitcoin price is looking
fine.
Can we get a pump song? All right, we
will get a pump song. What the heck?
What the heck? What's the worst that
could happen? I lose all my subscribers.
It's worth it.
It's worth it. All right, let's uh let's
see here.
Let's try and do a pump song. It's been
a while since we did a pump song.
It's been a real long while since we did
a pump song. I don't even know if I
remember how to do the pump song.
I don't know, guys. We have a red
candle.
I don't know. I'm sorry. I can't do the
pump song. I'm sorry. I can't do it. I
can't do it. I can't do it. I just
can't. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry,
guys. I can't do the pump song.
No offense. I I can't I can't bring
myself to do it now.
Oh man, I'm sorry guys.
Do the dump song.
We should do Bitcoin straight to 100K.
That's been a long time since we did
Bitcoin straight to 100K. Let me see a
blue candle. I definitely don't have
that in me, guys. Right now, I haven't I
haven't done fake metal vocals in a long
time.
I haven't done fake metal vocals in so
long. I don't think I can do them
anymore.
Whoa.
Hang on one second, guys.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, a couple months a down, we'll
bring the pump song back.
You know, why am I a farmer?
Is that a serious question? Why am I a
farmer?
Look, God created mankind and he he put
them in a garden to be gardeners. That's
our first job, you know. And the only
thing we really need in life is food.
And why would you waste time having
grass? It's so weird to me that people
have these manicured lawns. They pour
glyphosate on their Roundup weed killer
on their grass to make it look nice.
Meanwhile, what if what if the supply
chain shuts down and you can't go to the
grocery store?
You know what I'm saying?
It's like,
you know,
it's the most natural thing in the
world, the most human thing you could do
is grow your own food.
You know, that's why I'm a farmer. It's
just [music] it's the way it is. You
know, how do I get such good entries?
I'll tell you how, man. Not only do I
have the good entry, but I I did tell
the community I was taking it. Boom. So,
if you're in the Casper Cruy app
discord, you knew about it and you knew
about it in advance, too, because we
were looking at this trade this morning.
All right, this is our trading plan for
the week. All right, short from here,
long from around here. And this is a
naked weekly, naked daily PC. We came
down into the zone. Honestly, I was on a
low time frame and we had some nice
bullish divergence there, right?
Honestly, we had a nice little bullish
dive, money flow coming up. I'm like,
you know what? Let me go for it. Take a
quick profit one.
I I I would assume this trade will get
stopped out for a very small win right
now because we are chop city and I don't
know it doesn't look so great but that's
how I was in the KKK. I was involved in
America's most notorious racist group.
Interesting
man. The the algorithm knows how to how
to grab Jason Casper's attention. Who
wouldn't want to listen to that guy's
story,
you know?
Um,
yeah, we'll do the pump song in the bull
market. All right. All right. And
straight Bitcoin straight to 100K in the
bull market. All right.
You want to be in my group? Well, don't
join the group. Honestly, don't join the
group unless you actually know how to
trade already. And it's it's a fun
group. It's a good group.
But, you know,
the the update, it's a very valuable
group. Honestly, you're going to learn
so much. But if if if unless you're
already like a a trader trading,
it's not a signals group. All right.
It's just a super fun group. I enjoy
being
Can I say my diet plan? You want to know
Jason Casper's diet plan?
Jason Casper's diet plan to stay stack
jacked and succulent.
I'll tell you my diet plan.
Why not move the stop loss up in case of
a drop? Cuz it will still stop me out in
a profit. But this is invalidation.
I'll tell you. I tell you I'll tell you
what I ate today. How about that? I'll
tell you what Jason Casper ate for
breakfast.
Jason Casper had a 2,216
calories for breakfast, 345 carbs,
45 gram of fat, and 120 g of protein.
And I had
six whole zucchinis
baked in the oven for an hour and 45
minutes. A cup of sauerkraut.
Two eggs
fresh from the farm. I had a can of wild
Pacific mackerel fish.
I had two sweet potatoes.
I had 725 g of blueberries.
200 gram of plain non-fat Greek yogurt,
[music] 30 gram of almond butter,
133 gram of buckwheat,
and I had half a scoop of Ancient
Nutrition unflavored bone broth protein
powder. That was my breakfast.
And that's pretty much
pretty much all that I eat. Stuff like
that.
All right.
Sorry, Splash Raw Films, man. I don't
mean to talk about my diet plan when
you're
when when you're fasting. All right.
Let's check out oil real quick. Let's
check out CL CL.
Wow.
Did something happen? I heard there was
some kind of news with Trump or
something.
Look at that beautiful back test of the
trend line. Look at that crazy beautiful
back test of the support resistance
flip. That is insane. Right into the
golden pocket. Now we're reclaiming the
PC.
Let's see. Let's pull the We We bounced
from the macro golden pocket. Let's pull
the local golden pocket. We We filled
that gap. We perfectly filled the gap.
We back test the trend line. Beautiful
bounce. Bouncing once again from the
golden pocket. Trigger wave on the
daily.
I wouldn't be surprised if we don't see
oil
coming right up to around here.
Next,
let's check out the weekly.
It's looking looking not so bad.
I like the daily. I like that deep
oversold anchor. And now the trigger
we're getting with the money flow coming
up. Oil's looking pretty juicy.
Did I say fish from a can? I did say
fish from a can. Dave Digital. Yeah,
when I'm in a pinch, I eat fish from a
can. So, usually I have like ground beef
ready to go in the fridge, but I didn't
today. So, I opened up a can of
mackerel.
A can of mackerel. A great honestly. And
mackerel and sardines. If you can get
like uh what's what's a good brand for
that is like Wild Planet where they say
they don't use a BPA liner in the can.
At least they say it. At least it makes
you feel good. And look, if you're an
alpha rooster like me, a little BPA
never hurt anybody. You know what I'm
saying? But yeah, a little canned
mackerel from Wild Planet or sardines
is a quick go-to protein source with
lots of omega-3 polyunsaturated fatty
acids.
You know, lowers inflammation,
all that kind of good stuff.
I grew very little of that. You're
right. The only things I actually
produced on my home for that was
zucchinis and eggs. Everything else was
bought from the store. Everything else
was bought from the store.
bought from the store. But in general,
most of the food that I eat here, most
of the food, most of the food that we
eat here, we either do produce it
ourselves or we get it locally. We get
it locally from local farms that we know
the people and know the animals. So, our
dairy,
most of it, not not every single thing
obviously, but most of it we buy from
the farm. Our dairy, our meat, our fish
that we eat that's not from a can is
wild caught and we buy it through a
local farm that gets it from a good
source.
But then, you know, vegetables,
potatoes, squash, beans, all that stuff,
eggs, chicken, [music]
we raise that all here on the homestead,
baby.
CL about to do a CDW of the highs. Yeah.
Can you imagine if oil just pumps and
cranks? Pumps and cranks right up like
that. That would be crazy.
How tall am I? I am 8 foot seven. 8 foot
seven.
Just kidding.
Did I see the company saying they used
avocado to fry with was lying and it was
canola? Nah, I didn't see that, man. But
you know what? That's that's why I don't
eat anything fried in anything unless
I'm frying it myself.
You know,
nice shout out to Jay Becker with a
porttoella mushroom. That's what's up,
man. Oh, I forgot to mention, I didn't
even list this, but I did have one
shiakei mushroom. one shiakei mushroom
as well with my breakfast cuz you know
shiakei mushrooms are very good for you.
Shiakei and I think the other taki
mushroom it's all really good for you or
so they say. Remember they knows
everything. They know everything.
All
right. That is crazy though.
All right. You know what though, guys?
You know what?
I think we might get the pump. I think
we might get the pump. I think we might
get the pump. What do you guys think?
Will we get the pump? Yay or nay?
Yay or nay?
Should I take profit now? Should I take
out half the trade and lock in a nice
$2,000 profit? Let's take a poll. Let's
take a poll.
Should I close half?
I have 800K on the trade. I have 800K on
the trade.
If I close half now, I'll I'll close the
trade with a $2,000 profit locked in. Of
course, if I close half now, we're going
to pump straight up and squeeze all of
this. If I close the trade now, as soon
as I close the trade, boom. All right.
If I keep it open, we'll probably do
something like this.
And then boom. All right. So, if I close
the trade now, we'll pump straight up.
If I keep it open, we I'll get stopped
out and then we'll pump. That's just how
it works. All right.
Yeah, confirmations are not solid. This
is a scout trade. This a scout trade.
Wow. 78% say no. That's crazy. I should
Let's take another poll.
Should
I close half?
The answers are yes, no, or add another
800K.
All right, let's see now what you guys
say.
Let's see.
Can Bitra Can Bit Crra Bitcoin reclaim
65K? Of course it can. Anything's
possible, my friend. [music]
Anything is possible. Of course it can.
Of course it can. Here we go, baby.
This is so dumb. How come? How come
before the stream starts, we have hours
of downside, beautiful dumbbon as we go
live, baby. Sideways forever.
That's just how it is.
How much is my body fat? That's a good
question. I have no idea. I really have
no idea.
I'd say I'm probably at like 15%.
Between 12 and 15 is what I'd probably
say.
I don't really know. I don't really
know.
I don't know. I'd say I'm probably
between 12 and 15% body fat. I never
measure it. You know what I'm saying? I
don't measure it.
I'm looking at pictures of myself now. I
take progress photos.
I take progress photos of myself.
All right, you can tell me how much body
fat is this.
How much body fat is this? I'd say
that's 15%. Between 12 and 15%.
You can see the fat.
If it was leaner than 12%, I would have
like insane definition everywhere,
you know? Whoops.
What do you guys say? I say that's like
between 12 and 15% body fat, which I
feel like is like the I feel like that's
a healthy that is the healthy that is
how you should be. Like everyone should
like live at that. That's healthy.
You're going to feel good. You're going
to be strong. You're going to sleep
good. You're going to look good. You're
going to be able to eat a lot. all that
stuff. Big shout out to the super chat.
Stick to your predetermined trade plan.
Well, my predetermined trade plan,
honestly, on this one, I should have I
should have closed half. You guys really
did me dirty with this one. You guys
really did me dirty with this one. I was
up two grand. I said close half. You
guys said no.
My trade plan is to take a scalp and
then look for another. So, I've already
locked in like over a $500 profit.
Honestly, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I'm going to stick to my
predetermined plan.
Don't you worry. But let's see
what's the stop loss of the position. I
mean, it's right here on the screen. You
trying to stop hunt me? Let's see what
the poll says here.
That's so funny cuz
78% said no before. Now 38% say add
another. Okay, I guess I have to do what
the poll says. Add another 800,000.
Oh man, am I really about to do this?
Heck no, I'm not about to do this.
Heck no, I ain't about to do this.
You know,
I know the poll says to add 800K. Oh
man.
All right, guys. You know what? I think
I'm going to head out. You know, I got
some work to do around the farm. And
and after I do that, I got to spend time
with the fam. So, I love you guys. God
bless you guys. And I'll see you later.
Peace.